so this is the situation we have for
this patch this is what we are
broadcasting this cycle this is what we
have in our reservation stations and the
question is why hasn't this instruction
here in a rs3 dispatch before this
because obviously it's not waiting for
anything at this point
so the question is if this is the
beginning of a cycle then why hasn't
this already executed before we go to
this cycle the first choice is it was
issued in the previous cycle so
basically this says that this
instruction was inserted here in the
previous cycle so that's why it didn't
dispatch yet the next answer is another
instruction was dispatched to the ad
unit so this one couldn't and the third
answer is that if the instruction in RS
2 is older than the instruction in the
rs3 it comes before it in program order
then RS 3 cannot dispatch until rstudio
so simple this instruction cannot
dispatch because it's waiting for
something in this quiz you need to
select all answers that would possibly
be correct